<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MosqueZone</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer">NavigationDrawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_maps2">Map</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="before_entering">اللّهُـمَّ افْتَـحْ لي أَبْوابَ رَحْمَتـِك</string>
    <string name="before_entering1">O Allaah, I seek of You Your Grace..</string>
    <string name="exits_Masjid">اللّهُـمَّ إِنّـي أَسْأَلُكَ مِـنْ فَضْـلِك</string>
    <string name="exits_Masjid1">O Allaah, open the doors of Your Mercy for me.</string>
    <string name="Leaving_Home">بِسْمِ اللهِ تَوَكَّلْتُ عَلىَ اللهِ وَلاَ حَوْلَ وَلاَ قُوَّةَ اِلاَّ بِاللهِ ط</string>
    <string name="Leaving_Home1">Al’laah’s Name we begin with, I place my (full) trust in Al’laah and there is no Might and Power except with Al’laah.</string>
    <string name="Entering_Home">بِسْـمِ اللهِ وَلَجْنـا، وَبِسْـمِ اللهِ خَـرَجْنـا، وَعَلـى رَبِّنـا تَوَكّلْـنا</string>
    <string name="Entering_Home1">In the Name of Allah we enter, in the Name of Allah we leave, and upon our Lord we depend [then say As-Salaamu ‘Alaykum to those present</string>
    <string name="Feeling_Stressed">لآَ اِلَهَ اِلاَّ اللهُ الْحَلِيْمُ الْحَكِيْمُ لآَ اِلَهَ اِلاَّ اللهُ رَبُّ الْعَرْشِ الْعَظِيْم
لآَ اِلَهَ اِلاَّ اللهُ رَبُّ السَّمَاوَاتَ وَاْلاَرْضِ وَرَبُّ الْعَرْشِ الْكَرِيْمِ ط
    </string>
    <string name="Feeling_Stressed1">There is none worthy of worship except Al’laah, The Fore-bearing,
        The All Wise. There is none worthy of worship except Al’laah, The Lord of the Exalted Throne.
        There is none worthy of worship except Al’laah,
        The Lord of the Skies and The Lord of the Earth and the Lord of the distinguished Throne”.</string>
    <string name="After_rainfall">مُطِرْنَا بِفَضْلِ اللهِ وَ رَحْمَتِهِ </string>
    <string name="After_rainfall1">We have been given rain by the grace and mercy of Allah </string>
    <string name="Before_sleeping">بِاسْمِكَ رَبِّي وَضَعْتُ جَنْبِي، وَبِكَ أَرْفَعُهُ، فَإِنْ أَمْسَكْتَ نَفْسِي فَارْحَمْهَا، وَإِنْ أَرْسَلْتَهَا فَاحْفَظْهَا، بِمَا تَحْفَظُ بِهِ عِبَادَكَ الصَّالِحِينَ</string>
    <string name="Before_sleeping1">In Your name my Lord, I lie down and in Your name I rise, so if You should take my soul then have mercy upon it, and if You should return my soul then protect it in the manner You do so with Your righteous servants.</string>
    <string name="healthy_life">اللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في بَدَنـي ، اللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في سَمْـعي ، اللّهُـمَّ عافِـني في بَصَـري ، لا إلهَ إلاّ أَنْـتَ. اللّهُـمَّ إِنّـي أَعـوذُبِكَ مِنَ الْكُـفر ، وَالفَـقْر ، وَأَعـوذُبِكَ مِنْ عَذابِ القَـبْر ، لا إلهَ إلاّ أَنْـتَ</string>
    <string name="healthy_life1">O Allah, make me healthy in my body. O Allah, preserve for me my hearing. O Allah, preserve for me my sight. There is none worthy of worship but You . O Allah , I seek refuge in You from disbelief and poverty and I seek refuge in You from the punishment of the grave . There is none worthy of worship but You.</string>
    <string name="Everyday_Duas">اللَّهُمَّ إِنِّي أَسْأَلُكَ عِلْماً نَافِعاً، وَرِزْقاً طَيِّباً، وَعَمَلاً مُتَقَبَّلاً</string>
    <string name="Everyday_Duas1">O Allah, I ask You for knowledge that is of benefit , a good provision , and deeds that will be accepted.</string>
    <string name="For_forgiveness">رَبِّ اِنِّىْٓ اَعُوْذُ بِكَ اَنْ اَسْـــَٔـلَكَ مَا لَيْسَ لِيْ بِهٖ عِلْمٌ ۭ وَاِلَّا تَغْفِرْ لِيْ وَتَرْحَمْنِيْٓ اَكُنْ مِّنَ الْخٰسِرِيْنَ</string>
    <string name="For_forgiveness1">O my Lord! I seek refuge with You from asking You that of which I have no knowledge. And unless You forgive me and have Mercy on me, I would indeed be one of the losers.</string>

</resources>
